# Nguyen Anh Binh

# INTERN

## PERSONAL SUMMARY

Working and dedication at the company to experience the professional environment. In 5 years, becoming an well engineer with a high level of expertise, mastering the profession and important skills to give the best to the business.

## CONTACT

Mobile: 0373746940

Address: 223A Hoang Dieu 2,Linh

Trung, Thu Duc ,Tp.HCM

Email: anhbinh2704@gmail.com

Github:

https://github.com/nguyenanhbinh270

42002 Youtube :

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC 0oYoPJ5HgKZQSCdZk2K9fg

## **EDUCATION**

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology and Education

Course: Mechatronics Engineering

TOEIC: 580/990 GPA: 7.87/10.0

## **INTERESTS**

- Swimming
- · Reading books in the free time
- Play football

#### **ACTIVITIES**

• Participation: supporting the student to clear the room at school in the campaign "Green Sunday".

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 21/3/2023-30/5/2023

EMBEDDED ACADEMY TRAINING COURSE BY BOSCH Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

CAN protocol, Automotive basics, Testing, SW Development, Safety and Security

## 2/2022-5/2022

- Calculation and design of electronic boards while studying the subject " Power electronics "
- Designed and implemented an autonomous line-following robot using PIC16F887

#### 8/2022-12/2022

- Calculation and design model "Robot Scara 3DoF" while studying the subject "The Industrial Robots" such as
- 3D design with SolidWorks.
- Programming on Arduino using forward and inverse kinematics for robot control.
- Testing and debugging errors

#### SKILLS

- Intermediate-level English (TOEIC 580)
- Proficient in programming languages: C, C++, C#, python
- Knowledge of sensors, encoder and servo system in the industry
- Have knowledge about PLC S71200
- Basic knowledge with embedded platforms such as Arduino, Raspberry Pi, STM32, PIC, and ARM Cortex-M
- Communication protocols such as I2C, SPI, UART, MODBUS and CAN.
- Knowledge of circuit design, schematic capture, and PCB layout using software Protues.
- Basic knowledge about some design software: Autocad 2D.
- Basic knowledge of Linux, ROS, and Gazebo Simulation
- •Be able to use Robot Studio, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, and Keil C
- Ability to debug and troubleshoot hardware and software issues.
- Communication skills and ability to work in a team environment.
- Adaptable and resistant to high pressure from the working environment.